Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - A-D
        - Dolby, Thomas - The flat Earth, 1984; SR-21208; Dolby, Thomas (Box 27)
          Catalog # ST-12309; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12309 F-7
        - Don Yute - Bounce ya head back; Jonkonoo twist, 2001; SR-21209; Don Yute (Box 27)
          Catalog # ORA12011; A-side Matrix # ORA 12 011-A1
          Oracabessa Records
        - Donaldson, Lou - Color as a way of life, 1977; SR-21210; Donaldson, Lou (Box 27)
          Catalog # SD 9915; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-773789-A AT (PR)P
        - Doo Dew Kidz - Club secrets, 2001; SR-21211; Doo Dew Kidz; DJ Booman; Jones, Jimmy (Box 27)
          Catalog # DDK-002; A-side Matrix # DDK-A 002
          DDK Records
        - Doo Dew Kidz - Out my way; I'm so high, 1996; SR-21212; Doo Dew Kidz (Box 27)
          Catalog # HH11; A-side Matrix # HH 11- THIS SIDE
          Hardhead Records
        - Doobie Brothers - Farewell tour, 1983; SR-21213; Doobie Brothers (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21214. Double album.
          Catalog # 1-23772; A-side Matrix # 1-23772-A-SH1 0 B-18192-SH1 SLM 4588 1-1
        - Doobie Brothers - Farewell tour, 1983; SR-21214; Doobie Brothers (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21213. Double album.
          Catalog # 1-23772; A-side Matrix # 1-23772-C-SH2 0 B-18194-SH2 SLM 4589 1-1
        - Dope, Kenny - Dope beats volume 2, 1994; SR-25067; Dope, Kenny (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-25068. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # CR-2013-EP; A-side Matrix # CR-2013-EP-A-SIDE MADD
          Cuttin' Hip Hop
        - Dope, Kenny - Dope beats volume 2, 1994; SR-25068; Dope, Kenny (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-25067. Multiple copies.
        - Dore, Charlie - Listen, 1981; SR-21215; Dore, Charlie (Box 27)
          Catalog # CHR 1325; A-side Matrix # CHR 1325-AJ-1A
          Chrysalis
        - Doss, Kenny - Movin' on a feelin', 1980; SR-21216; Doss, Kenny (Box 27)
          Catalog # BRK 6997; A-side Matrix # BRK-1-6997-LW1
          Bearsville Records
          Bearsville, New York
        - Double - Blue, 1986; SR-21217; Double (Box 27)
          Catalog # SP-05133; A-side Matrix # AM SP 05133-A RCA1
        - Double Dee - Found love, 1990; SR-21218; Double Dee; Tenaglia, Danny (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21219. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # AED 73548; A-side Matrix # XSS 73548A-1A G1 VLADO A3
        - Double Dee - Found love, 1990; SR-21219; Double Dee; Tenaglia, Danny (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21218. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # AED 73548; A-side Matrix # XSS 73548A-2A G1 (A) A4 EPIC+IRMA=FOUNDLOVE…CIAO!
        - Douglas, Carol - Come into my life, 1978; SR-21220; Douglas, Carol (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21221. Different Discs. Promo
          Catalog # MSI-007; A-side Matrix # C-1 MSI-007A RE FIWtc
          Midsong International Records
        - Douglas, Carol - I got the answer, 1978; SR-21221; Douglas, Carol; Carmichael, Greg; Williams, Esther (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21220. Different Discs. Promo
          Catalog # MD 512; A-side Matrix # A-1 MD512B FIWtc
        - Douma, Danny - Night eyes, 1979; SR-21222; Douma, Danny (Box 27)
          Catalog # BSK 3326; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3326 LIU2 F2
        - Dr. Buzzard's Original Savannah Band - James Monroe H.S presents Dr. Buzzard's Original Savannah Band goes to Washington, 1979; SR-21223; Dr. Buzzard's Original Savannah Band (Box 27)
          Catalog # 6E-218; A-side Matrix # 6E218 A-Re SP
        - Dr. Dre - 2001 (disc one), 1999; SR-21224; Dr. Dre (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21225. Double album.
          Catalog # 069490487-1; A-side Matrix # 069490487-1A S-42226
        - Dr. Dre - 2001 (disc two), 1999; SR-21225; Dr. Dre (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21224. Double album.
          Catalog # 069490488-1; A-side Matrix # 069490488-1C S-42228
        - Dr. Freshh - Outlaw's dance, 1985; SR-21226; Dr. Freshh (Box 27)
          Catalog # ZK006; A-side Matrix # ZK06A CSB
          Zakia Records
        - Dr. Funnkenstein - Scratchin to the funk', 1985; SR-21227; Dr. Funnkenstein; DJ Cash Money (Box 27)
          Catalog # TTED-3014; A-side Matrix # TDE-3014-A VIRTUE CST
          Sound Makers Records
          Westville, New Jersey
        - Dr. Hook - Live, 1981; SR-21228; Dr. Hook (Box 28)
          Catalog # ST-12114; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12114 F-11 #3
        - Dr. Hook - Sometimes you win, 1979; SR-21229; Dr. Hook (Box 28)
          Catalog # SOO-12023; A-side Matrix # F-2
        - Dr. John - Tango place, 1979; SR-21230; Dr. John (Box 28)
          Catalog # SP-740; A-side Matrix # T SP-740-A-T4 M-S B
          Horizon Records
        - Dr. Sabara - Rap da esperança II; Dança do toma, to, toma, 1995; SR-21231; Dr. Sabara; MC Osmar; Moreno (Box 28)
          Catalog # 443.028; A-side Matrix # 443028-A
          Afegan
          Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
        - Dr. Sabara - Vamos dançar (vem, vem); Rap do apelo, 1995; SR-25076; Dr. Sabara; MC Osmar (Box 28)
          Catalog # 443.027; A-side Matrix # 443027 A
        - Dr. Soca - Merchant, 1979; SR-21232; Dr. Soca (Box 28)
          Catalog # MCR 001; A-side Matrix # MCR-101-A F/Wtc
          Brooklyn New York
        - Dr. Strut - Dr.Strut, 1979; SR-21233; Dr. Strut (Box 28)
          Catalog # M7-924 R1; A-side Matrix # M7-924R1 (A) 18A
        - Dramatics - The Dramatics live, 1988; SR-21234; Dramatics (Box 28)
          Catalog # SX 018; A-side Matrix # DMC-4536 A-1/9-88
          Stax Records
          West Germany
        - Dread, Mikey - S.w.a.l.k., 1982; SR-21235; Dread, Mikey (Box 28)
          Catalog # 40646; A-side Matrix # 406 46 A ROU-HB-09 A
          Heartbeat Records
          Sommerville, Massachusetts
        - Dread, Mikey - Beyond World War 3, 1981; SR-21236; Dread, Mikey (Box 28)
          Catalog # 39202; A-side Matrix # 02-A 39202-A
        - Dream Express - Dream Express, 1979; SR-21237; Dream Express (Box 28)
          Catalog # MCA-3159; A-side Matrix # MCA-1808-A 1
        - Dream Express - Dream Express, 1979; SR-21238; Dream Express (Box 28)
          Catalog # MCA-3159; A-side Matrix # MCA-1808-ASR 1
        - Dreamcatcher - In a ocean of joy, 1997; SR-21239; Dreamcatcher (Box 28)
          Catalog # 12 MNG 827; A-side Matrix # MPO 12 MNG 827 A
        - Drennon, Eddie - It don't mean a thing, 1978; SR-21240; Drennon, Eddie (Box 28)
          Catalog # NBLP 7095; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7095-AS-1-CP
        - Dru Hill - Enter the Dru (disc one), 1998; SR-21241; Dru Hill (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-21242. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # PRLP 7970; A-side Matrix # PRLP-7970-1-AS/H5
        - Dru Hill - Enter the Dru (disc two), 1998; SR-21242; Dru Hill (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-21241. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # PRLP 7970; A-side Matrix # PRLP-7970-1-CS/H5
        - Dschinghis Khan - Dschinghis Khan, 1980; SR-21243; Dschinghis Khan (Box 28)
          Catalog # EDI 60590; A-side Matrix # EDI-60590-A
          Musart
          Mexico
        - Clear the air; Serious - D.T., 1998; SR-21244; Clear the air; Serious (Box 28)
          Catalog # EAST 20; A-side Matrix # EAST+20+AA
          Eastside Records
        - Duces Wild - Gimmick, 1984; SR-21245; Duces Wild (Box 28)
          Catalog # NP 50018 P; A-side Matrix # NP-50018-A-1
          Next Plateau Records Inc.
        - Duke, George - I heard the blues, she heard my cry, 1980; SR-21246; Duke, George (Box 28)
          Catalog # PR7070; A-side Matrix # PR7070 A L-2163
          Pausa Records
        - Duke, George - Shine on; Positive energy, 1982; SR-21247; Duke, George (Box 28)
          Catalog # AS 1378; A-side Matrix # XSS-168910-1A
        - Duke, George - From me to you, 1977; SR-21248; Duke, George (Box 28)
          Catalog # PE 34469; A-side Matrix # PAL-34469-P-1D
        - Dudek, Les - Gypsy ride, 1981; SR-21249; Dudek, Les (Box 28)
          Catalog # FC 36798; A-side Matrix # PAL-36798-1H
        - Dudek, Les - Say no more, 1977; SR-21250; Dudek, Les (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-21251. Multiple copies. Promo
          Catalog # PC 34397; A-side Matrix # PAL-34397 1-C
        - Dudek, Les - Say no more, 1977; SR-21251; Dudek, Les (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-21250. Multiple copies. Promo
        - Duke of Burlington - Flash !, 2000; SR-21252; Duke of Burlington (Box 28)
          Catalog # WLP003; A-side Matrix # AE 20688/A
          Wah Wah Records
          Barcelona, Spain
        - Dukes - The Dukes Bugatti & Musker, 1982; SR-21253; Dukes (Box 28)
          Catalog # 80010-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-824951-C
        - DukeyMan - Hoody hood rat EP, 2003; SR-21254; DukeyMan (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-21255. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # MMR-2; A-side Matrix # MMR-2A
          Music Madness Recordings
        - DukeyMan - Hoody hood rat EP, 2003; SR-21255; DukeyMan (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-21254. Multiple copies.
        - DukeyMan - Milford & Eutaw EP, 2001; SR-21256; DukeyMan; DJ Technics (Box 28)
          Catalog # BB-400; A-side Matrix # BB400-9903X26-A
        - DukeyMan - Rockwilder; Club fiesta, 2002; SR-21257; DukeyMan (Box 28)
          Catalog # KOK-12; A-side Matrix # KOK-12 A
          King of Klub
        - DukeyMan - DukeyMan 2000, 2000; SR-21258; DukeyMan (Box 28)
          Catalog # CBS-01; A-side Matrix # 0005X36-A A+R
        - DukeyMan - The knuckleheads "EP" (Part 1), 1998; SR-25077; DukeyMan; DJ Technics (Box 28)
          Catalog # BB KH-100; A-side Matrix # 9807X04-A
        - DukeyMan - The knuckleheads "EP" (Part 2), 1998; SR-25078; DukeyMan; DJ Technics (Box 28)
          Catalog # BB KH-101; A-side Matrix # 9807X05-A
        - DukeyMan - The lollipop remix project, 2003; SR-25079; DukeyMan (Box 28)
          Catalog # CTX-7; A-side Matrix # CTX-7A
        - DukeyMan - Club on time; Marvins theme, 2002; SR-25080; DukeyMan; DJ Technics (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-25081
          Catalog # KOK-6; A-side Matrix # KOK-6 A
        - Various - Club King Records various artists vol. 2, 2002; SR-25081 (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-25080
          Catalog # CKR VA 02; A-side Matrix # CKR VA 002-A
          Club Kings
        - Duncan, Darryl - Heaven, 1988; SR-21259; Duncan, Darryl (Box 28)
          Catalog # 6237 ML; A-side Matrix # 6237-ML-A YYM 15B #12
        - Dungeon Family - Even in darkness (disc one), 2001; SR-21260; Dungeon Family (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-21261. Double album.
          Catalog # 07822-14693-1; A-side Matrix # 0782214693-15A TIPPY-Hit Factory
        - Dungeon Family - Even in darkness (disc two), 2001; SR-21261; Dungeon Family (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-21260. Double album.
          Catalog # 07822-14693-1; A-side Matrix # 07822 14693-15C TIPPY-HFM
        - Dunkley, Errol - O.K. Fred, 1979; SR-21262; Dunkley, Errol (Box 28)
          Catalog # CEL 2-006543; A-side Matrix # LTM 1043 A
          Celluloid
        - Dunlap, Gene - Party in me, 1981; SR-21263; Dunlap, Gene (Box 28)
          Catalog # ST-12190; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12190-Z1
        - Dunn & Bruce Street - Shout for joy; If you come with me, 1982; SR-21264; Dunn & Bruce Street (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-21265. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # DK 12-902; A-side Matrix # DK-12 902 -A- 004121222 PRC-C-1-1-1
          Devaki Records
          Cleveland, Ohio
        - Dunn & Bruce Street - Shout for joy; If you come with me, 1982; SR-21265; Dunn & Bruce Street (Box 28)
          In same jacket as # SR-21264. Multiple copies.
        - Dupree, Robbie - Robbie Dupree, 1980; SR-21266; Dupree, Robbie (Box 28)
          Catalog # 6E-273; A-side Matrix # 6E-273 A-1 AR B-14973
        - Duran Duran - Is there something I should know? (Monster mix), 1983; SR-21267; Duran Duran (Box 28)
          Catalog # 8551; A-side Matrix # 8551-X600639-A- G-1
        - Duran Duran - Notorious, 1986; SR-21268; Duran Duran (Box 28)
          Catalog # PJ-12540; A-side Matrix # PJ-1-12540-Z1-DMM MASTERDISK
        - Dury, Ian - New boots and panties!!, 1978; SR-21269; Dury, Ian (Box 28)
          Catalog # STF 0002; A-side Matrix # STF-0002-SA-1A
          Stiff Records
        - Ian Dury & the Blockheads - Do it yourself, 1979; SR-21270; Ian Dury & the Blockheads; Dury, Ian (Box 28)
          Catalog # SEEZ 14; A-side Matrix # SEEZ-14-A3-UT
        - Dynamic Breakers - Kim, 1985; SR-21271; Dynamic Breakers (Box 28)
          Catalog # SUN 428DJ; A-side Matrix # A- SUN 428A
        - Dynamic Superiors - Give & take, 1977; SR-21272; Dynamic Superiors (Box 28)
          Catalog # M6-879S1; A-side Matrix # M6-87951-2707-S-REI-06A
        - Dynasty - Love in the fast lane, 1981; SR-21273; Dynasty (Box 28)
          Catalog # AS-11529; A-side Matrix # AM-11529-A SP
        - Dynasty - Your piece of the rock, 1979; SR-21274; Dynasty (Box 28)
          Catalog # BXL1-3398; A-side Matrix # BXL1-33938-A 1S
        - Dyson, Clifton - Body in motion, 1979; SR-21275; Dyson, Clifton (Box 28)
          Catalog # AA-373-LPD; A-side Matrix # 373-A 8179 LPD -2
          All-American
        - Dyson, Clifton - Body in motion, 1979; SR-21276; Dyson, Clifton (Box 28)
        - Dyson, Ronnie - The more you do it, 1976; SR-21277; Dyson, Ronnie (Box 28)
          Catalog # PC 34350; A-side Matrix # 1 AL 34350-1C